http://www.monitortools.com/privacypolicy/

Altaro Hyper-V Backup
More freeware tools ...
File System Monitoring
Internet of Things (IoT)
SNMP MIB
You are here:
MonitorTools.com > Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
General
This Privacy Policy aplies to the
web site (referred to herein as the "Web Site") of ActiveXperts Software B.V. (referred to herein by "ActiveXperts").
When a visitor requests pages from
site, our Web servers automatically recognize the browser's domain name, and IP address.
We collect the domain names and IP addresses in order to aggregate information on the pages users access or visit.
This information is collected solely for statistical purposes and is not used to identify individuals.
From time to time, we may ask users to provide an e-mail address or mailing address for the purpose of conducting a survey or to provide additional services (for example, subscriptions to e-mail newsletters).
Whenever the identity of a visitor is recorded, we will clearly indicate the purpose of the request before the information is requested.
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user.
Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site.
Some of our partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.
Security
This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information.
When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line.
When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number),
that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL.
While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Microsoft Internet Explorer and Google Chrome becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'.
To learn more about SSL, visit www.ssl.com.
Email-Newsletter List Privacy Policy
ActiveXperts maintains a strict "no-spam" policy. If you sign up for our free newsletter, your e-mail address will "not" be sold or given to any third party. If you have any questions or concerns, please contact us via email at:
Links
This web site contains links to other sites.
Please be aware that we ActiveXperts, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.
We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information.
This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.
Internet resource for ICT administrators and operators.
WindowsManagement.com
Internet Resource for Windows management software.
WindowsShareware.com
Internet Resource for Windows shareware software.
WindowsToolkits.com
Internet Resource for Windows toolkit software.
Contact Us
Terms of Use
Privacy Policy
Copyright © 2020 MonitorTools.com All rights reserved.
Developed by GXPMEDIA.COM
